

#### PROFILE

Having 4.4 years of experience developing web-based applications using MVC.NET, jQuery, Bootstrap, Angular and Entity Framework. Strong in Object Oriented Programming concepts. Flexibility and Adaptability in regards with new technologies and environments. Ability to work effectively with Global project teams. Excellent organizational ability in handling time critical and multi-tasking environment.

# CONTACT-

Sk

Clie

HT

CS

SA

BC JA

JQ

A١

A١

Mo

10

Ser

M

Des

**PHOTOSHOP** 

		+1 (816)-663-4868	
	mura	ali.ofc@outlook.com	<b>×</b>
in.linkedin.com/in/muralichukka			in
	https://chkrish	9.github.io/Portfolio	=
AWARDS-			
Y	Applause award (	April 2018) – Deloitte	
¥	Best coding aware HCL (India).	d (September 2015) –	
SKILLS			
HTN CSS SAS BOO JAV JQU ANO			
Mobile Technologies:			
Server Technologies: MVC.NET C# JAVA			
Designing tools:			

# **MURALI KRISHNA SAI CHUKKA**

# **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

# **EXPERIENCE**

2019

#### STUDENT DEVELOPER - UMKC

Maintaining the college web applications. Developing the new enhancements according to the college requirements.

2017 - 2018

#### **BUSINESS TECHNICAL ANALYST - DELOITTE**

Responsibilities include Development, Unit testing, defect analysis, defect fixing, client interaction for clarification, maintaining the code quality and standards.

2014 - 2017 (

# **SOFTWARE ENGINEER - HCL**

Joined as a campus hire and finished training on Microsoft technologies. Worked as a full stack developer.

#### **EDUCATION-**

2018 - 2020

**MASTER'S IN COMPUTER SCIENCE – PURSUING (Current GPA 4.0)** UNIVERSITY OF MISSOURI KANSAS CITY - USA (AUG 2018 - Present) Specialization in Web Development and Data Science.

2009 - 2013 (

**BACHELOR'S IN COMPUTER SCIENCE - 77.45 %** VELAGAPUDI RAMAKRISHNA SIDDHARTHA ENGINEERING COLLEGE - INDIA Specialization in Web Development, Data Structures, Software engineering development models.

#### PRO IECTS-

2018

# **FACTORY MAINTENANCE SYSTEM - UMKC**

- Implemented mobile application using ionic 3.
- Increased the performance of UI by storing static data like images, js files etc., on client-side database.
- Implemented Excel import functionality.

2017 - 2018

#### **TECO ENERGY - DELOITTE**

- Convert globalization functionality from resource files to database. Provided user interface in admin portal for translation.
- Design user interfaces for Agent portal.

2016 - 2017

#### **PANASONIC MMS - HCL**

- Redesigned entire application (74 web pages) using Bootstrap within a month.
- Implemented schedule back up of the database via web application.
- Increase the performance of the dashboard data by converting server-side code to stored procedures.

2015 - 2016

# **PANASONIC WIP - HCL**

- Setup base for the application using bootstrap and angularjs.
- Implemented dashboards using jsPlumb library.
- Implemented charts functionality in the application.

# 2014 - 2015

# **MEDTRONIC - HCL**

- Implemented a generic crud framework using bootstrap.
- Implemented import functionality.